{
    "subject": "resource/Emerson,_Lake_&_Palmer_(album)",
    "predicate": "ontology/artist",
    "object": "resource/Emerson,_Lake_&_Palmer",
    "human_readable": "The artist of Emerson, Lake & Palmer (album) is Emerson, Lake & Palmer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868265390396118,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the album 'Emerson, Lake & Palmer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9817078113555908,
            "question": "What is the name of the album by Emerson, Lake & Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.959527313709259,
            "question": "When was the album 'Emerson, Lake & Palmer' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9474031925201416,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs from the album 'Emerson, Lake & Palmer'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9390194416046143,
            "question": "Is Emerson, Lake & Palmer a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.930930495262146,
            "question": "Can you name any other albums by Emerson, Lake & Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9197349548339844,
            "question": "Who are the members of Emerson, Lake & Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8930666446685791,
            "question": "What genre of music is typically associated with Emerson, Lake & Palmer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.837441086769104,
            "question": "What instruments are featured prominently in Emerson, Lake & Palmer's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.707756757736206,
            "question": "Has Emerson, Lake & Palmer won any awards for their music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of Emerson, Lake & Palmer (album) is Emerson, Lake & Palmer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_433_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments are featured prominently in Emerson, Lake & Palmer's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_433_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is typically associated with Emerson, Lake & Palmer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_433_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the members of Emerson, Lake & Palmer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_433_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_433_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can say that the triple \"The artist of Emerson, Lake & Palmer (album) is Emerson, Lake & Palmer\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the band Emerson, Lake & Palmer and their debut album \"Emerson, Lake & Palmer,\" confirming that the artists of this album are indeed Emerson, Lake & Palmer themselves."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}